 [
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is performed by data scientist?",
    "choice1": "Define the quesion",
    "choice2": "Create reproducible code",
    "choice3": "Challenge results",
    "choice4": "All of above",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Which of the following is the most important language for data science?",
    "choice1": "Java",
    "choice2": "Ruby",
    "choice3": "R",
    "choice4": "None of above",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is one of the key data science skills?",
    "choice1": "Statistics",
    "choice2": "Machine learning",
    "choice3": "Data visualization",
    "choice4": "All of above",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Data fishing is sometimes referred as ______",
    "choice1": "Data bagging",
    "choice2": "Data dredging",
    "choice3": "Data merging",
    "choice4": "None of above",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which function gives information about top-level data?",
    "choice1": "tail",
    "choice2": "summary",
    "choice3": "head",
    "choice4": "None of above",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which technique comes under practical machine learning?",
    "choice1": "Bagging",
    "choice2": "Forecasting",
    "choice3": "Boosting",
    "choice4": "None of these",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "CNN is mostly used for which type of data?",
    "choice1": "structured data",
    "choice2": "unstructured data",
    "choice3": "Both",
    "choice4": "None of above",
    "answer": 2
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following is another name for raw data?",
    "choice1": "Destination data",
    "choice2": "Eggy data",
    "choice3": "Machine learning",
    "choice4": "Secondary data",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is revision control system?",
    "choice1": "Numpy",
    "choice2": "Git",
    "choice3": " Scipy",
    "choice4": "Slidify",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "A ______ is a structured representation of data",
    "choice1": "data table",
    "choice2": "functions",
    "choice3": "data prepration",
    "choice4": "data frame",
    "answer": 4
  },
]